Class of 1931 Records, 1927-1999
Smith College Archives
Class of 1931 Records
1927-1999
Smith College. Class of 1931.
RG 80 UUID:8dbb8d0e-1cbd-46ba-8f09-96c33f0f46da
12 boxes (5.4 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1931.
The Class of 1931 was the fifty-third graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1931 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1931, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1931 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Addresses 1929-1931 (Box 2028, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 2)
- Commencement Music 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 3)
- Commencement Photographs 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 4)
- Commencement Speaker 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 5)
- Freshman Handbook 1927-1928 (Box 2028, Folder 6)
- Groups 1927-1931 (Box 2028, Folder 7)
- History 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 8)
- Ivy Day 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 10)
- Junior Prom 1930 (Box 2028, Folder 11)
- Junior Ushers 1930 (Box 2028, Folder 12)
- Last Chapel 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 13)
- Class Letters 1946-1976 (Box 2028, Folder 14)
- Class Officer's Handbook 1991 (Box 2028, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1932 (Box 2028, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1936 (Box 2028, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1941 (Box 2028, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1946 (Box 2028, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1951 (Box 2028, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1956 (Box 2028, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1961 (Box 2028, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1966 (Box 2028, Folder 23)
- Reunions 1971 (Box 2028, Folder 24)
- Reunions 1976 (Box 2028, Folder 25)
- Reunions-Recollections 1981 (Box 2028, Folder 26)
- Reunions undated (Box 2028, Folder 27)
- Reunions-Reunion Songs undated (Box 2028, Folder 28)
- Class Secretary's Records-Name/Address Change Lists 1986-1989 (Box 2028.1, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Records-Name/Address Change Lists 1989-1997 (Box 2028.1, Folder 2)
- Class secretary's Records-Change of Address Correspondence 1986-1994 (Box 2028.1, Folder 3)
- Class Secretary's Handbook 1992-1999 (Box 2028.1, Folder 4)
- Senior Dramatics 1931 (Box 2028.1, Folder 5)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1931 (Box 2028.1, Folder 6)
- Senior Questionnaire 1931 (Box 2028.1, Folder 7)
- Songs 1927-1931 (Box 2028.1, Folder 8)
- Sophomore Carnival 1929 (Box 2028.1, Folder 9)
- Sophomore Push 1929 (Box 2028.1, Folder 10)
- Step Sings 1931 (Box 2028.1, Folder 11)
- Class Supper 1931 (Box 2028.1, Folder 12)
- Class Secretary Card Files (Box OV)
- Reunion Costume (Box OV)